ebulksms.com 2016-06-28

# Our Privacy Policy - Best Bulk SMS Platform in Nigeria

Ebulk SMS is committed to protecting the privacy and security of our customers and will like to certify that our users are fully informed about the way information is collected and used. The following sets forth the policies for the collection and use of personally identifiable information by Ebulk SMS.

Ebulk SMS will not sell out your personal information for any reason, as we understand the need for your privacy

Ebulk SMS may use certain non-affiliated third parties as service providers, and may share non-public personal information with them in order to fulfil the services requested. While we carefully select trusted and reputable third-party companies with which to partner, Ebulk SMS is not responsible for the privacy practices of third-party partners or the privacy policies or content of third-party partner sites.

##### Use of Data Collected

We use your personal, demographic and profile data to enhance your experience at our site and to enable us to present content in which we think you may be interested. We use your contact information to send you information about our company and promotional material from our partners. We may also use your personal, demographic and profile data to improve our site, for statistical analysis, for marketing and promotional purposes, and for editorial or feedback purposes for our advertisers. Information collected by us may be added to our databases and used for future e-mails or postal mailings regarding site updates, new products and services, upcoming events, and/or status of orders placed online. 

##### Disclosure of Data to Third Parties

We may disclose data we collect to third parties as described below. If you choose to provide personal information, it may be used for the following purposes: (1) considering you for an account with the third-party company, (2) sharing of your information with trusted third parties such as financial services providers, (3) as required by law, and (4) for marketing products and services which we determine, in our sole judgment, that you might find of interest via mediums such as postal direct mail and tele-marketing. 

##### Changes to this Privacy Policy

We reserve the right to revise and update this Privacy Policy at any time by posting the changes online at our site, and will apply to all information collected by ebulksms.com both prior to and following the effective date. Your use of the Site following any such revisions will be deemed your acceptance of such revisions.
